Finding Aid for the Alfred H. Bartles Papers
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
- DETAILED CONTAINER LIST
  - Series A: Musical compositions—Manuscripts
    - Subseries 2: Sketchbooks
      - Reel-to-Reels (Box 14)
        - [Reel], Mar. 9, 1980: listed contents: 1. “Copy of Quintet made for me in Bönnigheim at 3% ips” - 2. Beersheba Neo-Baroque [Suite] - 3. Piano Sonata, Lisa [?Yilalys], Mar. 9, 1980, TA ips; recording only contains the Piano Sonata (Box 22, Folder 9)
        - “Excalibur-3 mal”, [n.d.]: Tennessee Tech Band (Box 22, Folder 10)
        - “Music for Symphony Orchestra and Jazz Ensemble”, May 1, 1968: American Music Festival, Eastman School of Music, stereo, 4 track (Box 22, Folder 11)
        - “Music for Symphony Orchestra and Jazz Ensemble”, Apr. 6,1966: Peabody-Vanderbilt Jazz Ensemble, Nashville Symphony Orchestra; Willis Page, conductor; J.F. Sawyer, director of jazz ensemble: 2 tracks stereo of 4 tracks (Box 22, Folder 12)
        - “Bartles Piano Quartet”, June 7,1968: New York City; contains performance of the Piano Quartet (Box 22, Folder 13)
        - “Jazz with Trio for Steve Knowlton, Aspen, Colo.”, Apr. 6, 1956: Barr, Herman, Wright, Fred Razutto, director; TA halftrack (Box 22, Folder 14)
        - ‘Theme in Three”, May 16, 1954: TA ips, monaural halftrack; performed by the Ohio University Orchestra; Karl Ahrendt, conductor (Box 22, Folder 15)
        - “Original Composition Program, Convocation Hall”, Jul. 24,1976: includes printed program; no listed compositions by Bartles; performances are all student compositions from the Sewanee Summer Music Festival (Box 22, Folder 16)
        - [Reel], [n.d.]: contains the Piano Quartet; recorded at Stereo Sound Studios, New York City; TA ips, monaural (Box 22, Folder 17)
        - “SSMC”, summer 1976: contents include Tone Sculpture No. I by Alfred H. Bartles (H. Temiankz, conductor); other contents of reel include Copland’s Appalachian Spring, Schumann’s Fairy Tales, and Gordon Jacob’s Sextet, with the faculty at SSMC performing (Martha S. Bartles, piano; [Alfred?], cello) (Box 22, Folder 18)
        - [Reel], 1968-1969: on side 1: Andrea Johnson, cello; Alfred Bartles, piano, playing Romberg E minor Sonata (Mar. 10, 1968) and Vivaldi E minor Sonata (Mar. 17, 1968); Isabel Bartles, piano: Clementi Sonatina in Cmajor (May 11, 1968), Bach Prelude, Kabalevsky Meadow Dance (Apr. 19, 1969), N.Y.C., TA ips, mono (Box 22, Folder 19)
        - [Reel], [n.d.]: listed contents: Exposure / John Lewis, arr. Alf Bartles - Ballad for Fig. Horn ([performed by?] E. Lehn); one track containing the Ballad, followed by Exposure (Box 22, Folder 20)
        - “313th Army Band Broadcast [?conversation] A.H.B. [?...] + M.H.B.”, [n.d.]; Alfred playing piano on broadcast; track includes: Sweet Sue - Over the Rainbow, arr. Alf Bartles - On the Sunny Side of the Street - Red Sails in the Sunset, arr. Alf Bartles; / Only Have Eyes for You; [unspecified tune] - The Little White Cloud That Cried; [unspecified tune] - Lady Bird, arr. Alf Bartles - Serenade in Blue, arr. Alf Bartles; does not contain any conversation between A.H.B. and M.H.B. (Box 22, Folder 21)
        - “Julia, Isabel, Michael, Alfred”, Sept. 6, 1971: no contents listed on container-contains assorted recordings of the Bartles family singing and playing their instruments (Box 22, Folder 22)
        - “Vanilla Music 7½ Tape Copy”, Dec. 21, 1964: contains One Day Late in May -1 Looked for Me - What Will I Do After You - Miss Amandah Lee (Box 22, Folder 23)
        - “Northeast Louisiana State College Jazz Ensemble”, May 17,1962: excerpts from spring concert in Brown Auditorium, Monroe, Louisiana; contents: Theme-Mr. Lucky - Louisiana Jazz Suite (Sawyer, Flg. Hr. & Trpt.) -Jordu-Da Haud-Capt. Ahab - Lady Be Good - Time After Time - From this Moment On - Between the Devil & the Deep Blue Sea (Box 22, Folder 24)
        - [Reel], Jul. 22, 1962: The Motel on the Mountain, parts I & II; performed by Alf Bartles and Dick Handel; reel is a live recording of a jazz duet set at the venue called “Motel on the Mountain” in New York (Box 22, Folder 25)
        - [Reel], Jul. 22, 1962: The Motel on the Mountain, part III; performed by Alf Bartles and Dick Handel; reel is a live recording of a jazz duet set at the venue called “Motel on the Mountain” in New York (Box 22, Folder 26)
      - Cassette Tapes/DATs Tape (Box 23)
        - “3 Complete Compositions of Alfred H. Bartles”, [n.d.]: Side B: Ballad (Box 23, Folder 1)
        - “Compositions of Alf Bartles”, [n.d.]: listed contents: Piano Sonata (played by Lisa Yilalys), Excalibur: an Heroic Episode for Band (performed by Tennessee Tech Band), Ballad for Flügel Horn & Jazz Ens. (performed by Ack van Rooyen and the SDR Big Band, conducted by Ervin Lehn) (Box 23, Folder 2)
        - “Fiocco / Bartles, Bach Cello-S.l, Veress Violin-Sonate, Trio per archi”, [n.d.]: cassette case labeled “Bob Ryman Tape One” (Box 23, Folder 3)
        - “AHB [?P]NO”, [n.d.] (Box 23, Folder 4)
        - “Ballad f. F.H. & J.E. - MFSOAJE”, [n.d.]: contains Ballad for Flugelhorn and Jazz Ensemble (performed by Matheson Phillips) and Music for Symphony Orchestra and Jazz Ensemble (Box 23, Folder 5)
        - “Ballad for Flugelhorn and Jazz. Ens. / Alf Bartles”, [n.d.] (Box 23, Folder 6)
        - “Rehearsal MFSOAJE”, [n.d.] (Box 23, Folder 7)
        - ‘The Nashville Symphony & The Nashville Jazz Machine”, [n.d.] (Box 23, Folder 8)
        - ‘The Nashville Symphony & The Nashville Jazz Machine”, [n.d.] (Box 23, Folder 9)
        - “Chicago: MFSO&JE”, [n.d.]: Side B: Ballad (Box 23, Folder 10)
        - “Music for Sym. Orch. and Jazz Ens - Revised”, [n.d.] (Box 23, Folder 11)
        - “I First Closed Position - for Juliana”, [n.d.]: Side B: “I 1st Clsd. Pos. & Repetition” (Box 23, Folder 12)
        - “Recital Pieces and Etudes for the advanced beginning Cellist-Vols. 1 & 2”, [n.d.]: by Alfred H. Bartles; performed by Alfred H. Bartles, cello; Martha S. Bartles, piano. (Box 23, Folder 13)
        - “AHB Recital P.: new master end & [?illegible]”, [n.d.] (Box 23, Folder 14)
        - ‘Three for Two-A. Bartles”, [n.d.]: performed by Julia Bartles, cello, and unnamed bassoon (Box 23, Folder 15)
        - “Bartles-Tubossa”, [n.d.] (Box 23, Folder 16)
        - “Northeast Louisiana State College Jazz”, May 17,1962: “Bartles & Handel - Motel on the Mountain”; cassette transfer from reel-to-reel? (Box 23, Folder 17)
        - “Bönnigheim 1973”, 1973?: contains lecture [by AHB?] (Box 23, Folder 18)
        - “Composition Recital - SSMC (1975)”, 1975? (Box 23, Folder 19)
        - “Original Compositions by Students of AHB, SSMC, 1976”, Jul. 24,1976 (Box 23, Folder 20)
        - “Ella & Basie, Liederhalle”, [n.d.]: Side B: Vor Vorspiel, Nov. 18, 1980, B.C.[?] (Box 23, Folder 21)
        - “AHB Solo Piano”, Jun. 25, 1986: “W. Gurmann [sp?]” (Box 23, Folder 22)
        - “AHB-Pno. 23-VI-87”, Jun. 23, 1987 (Box 23, Folder 23)
        - “Sewanee 7-24-87 Faculty”, Jul. 24, 1987: Respighi Sonata, “Kless - Bartles” (Box 23, Folder 24)
        - “Violin, Yair Kless, Piano, Martha Bartles”, Nov. 13,1987: Sonata / J.M. Le Clair - op. 12, no. 11 L. van Beethoven - Lyric Poem / A.H. Bartles - Sonata in B minor / O. Respighi. (Box 23, Folder 25)
        - “Alf Plays for Del - 4 II 90, Stgt.”, Feb. 4, 1990, Stuttgart: listed contents: Every time we say Goodby [i.e., Goodbye] - All the things - But Beautiful - Giant Steps - In a mello [i.e., mellow] tone - Day Dream - Don’t you know I care - Body & Soul (Box 23, Folder 26)
        - “Berg/Bartles Sonate, Op. 1”, Mar. 24, 1995, Funkstudio Berg: listed contents: Anmoderation (11:10) - Alban Berg: Sonate op. 1 (13:30) (Box 23, Folder 27)
        - “Berg Sonate für Kammerorchester, Op. 1”, Jun. 25,1991: SDR [Süddeutscher Rundfunk]; AHB (Box 23, Folder 28)
        - “Berg Sonate für Kammerorchester, Op. 1”, Jun. 25,1991: (Gronbach) (Box 23, Folder 29)
        - “Alf plays, 24 V 92”, May 24, 1992: listed contents: Every time we say goodbye (Box 23, Folder 30)
        - “AHB Piano, III, IV 94”, Mar.-Apr. 1994? (Box 23, Folder 31)
        - “When Canadians Waltz”, May 25, 1994: performed by the Süddeutscher Blechbläser Quintet in Neustadt (Box 23, Folder 32)
        - “Music for Symphony & Jazz Ensemble”, Oct. 1994: performed by the Nashville Symphony w/The Establishment (Box 23, Folder 33)
        - “AHB 8 XII 94[?]”, Dec. 8, 1994: listed contents: Wien, Wien-All the things; Repetition (Box 23, Folder 34)
        - “APC Concert 1995-96”, 1995-1996? (Box 23, Folder 35)
      - Cassette Tapes/DATs/Videotapes (Box 24)
        - [Unlabeled cassette tape], n.d.; Side A: Piano recital consisting of Beethoven, Chopin, Liszt, and Brahms [M. Bartles, piano?] - Side B: Martha Bartles speech on the event of Alfred’s 65th birthday, (1995) (Box 24, Folder 1)
        - ‘The Music of the Eurythmeum Stuttgart’s 1997 North American Tour”, 1997: performed by The Yerevan Trio; contents include music written for The Little Prince / Alfred Bartles. (Box 24, Folder 2)
        - ‘The NEW When Tubas Waltz”, Jun. 2000: recorded in Regina, Saskatchewan (Box 24, Folder 3)
        - “Epidaurus”, [n.d.]; DAT (Box 24, Folder 4)
        - “A. Bartles”, [n.d.]; DAT; listed contents: 3 for 2-Xmas Wish - Cello Recital Pieces & Etudes (Box 24, Folder 5)
        - “Recital Pieces & Etudes-Dolby B”, [n.d.]; contains both volume 1 and volume 2 (Box 24, Folder 6)
        - “Structural analysis, 5th Cello suite by J.S. Bach - A.H. Bartles”, [n.d.] (Box 24, Folder 7)
        - “Alfred”, [n.d.]; Maxell VHS-C PAL VX-30 videotape (Box 24, Folder 8)
        - “Alfred”, [n.d.]; Maxell VHS-C PAL VX-30 videotape (Box 24, Folder 9)
        - [Untitled], [n.d.]; Maxell VHS-C PAL VX-30 videotape (Box 24, Folder 10)
      - Compact discs/CD-ROMs/Other (Box 25)
        - “AHB at the Piano: 12 Song Demo”, [n.d.]: performance contains [Unknown] -[Unknown] - You’re the Top - You’d Be So Nice to Come Home To - Sophisticated Lady — Prelude to a Kiss - My Foolish Heart - [Unknown] - There Could Never Ever Be Another You- [Unknown] - Lullaby of the Leaves- [Unknown] - [Unknown] (Box 25, Folder 1)
        - “Alfred H. Bartles”, [n.d.]: contains: Sonata, Opus 1 for Chamber Orchestra / Alban Berg, Alfred Bartles (Sewanee Festival Orchestra, 2002) - Epidaurus - Three for Two -Sonata, Opus lfor Chamber Orchestra (South German Radio) - Alfred Bartles Interview with Hans Peter Jahn (Box 25, Folder 2)
        - “Alfred Bartles Compositions & Orchestrations”, [n.d.]: listed contents: Bêla Bartok 1st Rhapsody - Tubossa - Epidaurus - Three for two: Duo for bassoon & violoncello -Sonata opus 1 for chamber orchestra - Alfred Bartles interview w/Hans Peter Jahn; Berg recording is marked as flawed (Box 25, Folder 3)
        - “Orchestrations and Compositions” / Alfred H. Bartles, [n.d.]: performances contain First Rhapsody for Cello and Orchestra / Bartók/Bartles - Tubossa / Bartles - Epidaurus I Bartles - Three for Two / Bartles - Sonata for Chamber Orchestra / Berg, Bartles (Box 25, Folder 4)
        - “A Christmas Wish” / lyrics: Beegie Adair, music: Alfred H. Bartles, [n.d.]: played by Lisa Yilalys, piano and Alfred Bartles, vocals (Box 25, Folder 5)
        - “A Christmas Wish” / lyrics: Beegie Adair, music: Alfred H. Bartles, [n.d.]: played by Lisa Yilalys, piano and Alfred Bartles, vocals (Box 25, Folder 6)
        - “Music for Symphony Orchestra & Jazz Ensemble” / by Alfred Bartles, [n.d.]: The Nashville Symphony & The Jazz Machine, Jay Dawson, conducting (Box 25, Folder 7)
        - “Music for Symphony Orchestra and Jazz Ensemble” / Alfred H. Bartles, [n.d.]: performed by the Nashville Symphony Orchestra and The Jazz Machine, Jay Dawson, conductor; designated as archival recording only (Box 25, Folder 8)
        - “Recital Pieces and Etudes for the Advanced Beginning Cellist: Volumes I and II”, [n.d.]: performed by Julia Bartles Emahiser, cello, Lisa Yilalys, piano (Box 25, Folder 9)
        - “Recital Pieces and Etudes for the Advanced Beginning Cellist: Volumes I and II”, [n.d.]: performed by Julia Bartles Emahiser, cello, Lisa Yilalys, piano; introductions by Alfred H. Bartles (Box 25, Folder 10)
        - “Recital Pieces & Etudes for the Advanced Beginning Cellist”, [n.d.]: audio back-up CD-R; Julia Bartles Emahiser, cello, Lisa Yilalys, piano (Box 25, Folder 11)
        - “Recital Pieces & Etudes for the Advanced Beginning Cellist”, [n.d.]: CD-R; Julia Bartles Emahiser, cello, Lisa Yilalys, piano; marked: “corrupt?” (Box 25, Folder 12)
        - “Roumanian Br. Quintet” / Bartók/Bartles [CD-R 80], [n.d.]: contains .ETF and .MUS files for the Bartles brass quintet arrangement of Bartók’s Romanian Folk Dances (Box 25, Folder 13)
        - [Attic Archival Series from Bill Russell], ca. early 1950s: “These tracks are completes and partíais...vignettes of jazz times, places and people in the environs of Ole Miss: tracks: Riff (/ got rhythm changes) - LadyBird- Blue Moon - What’s New-Jumping with Symphony Sid - All the Thing You Are -1 Surrender Dear/Body & Soul - Out of Nowhere - Riff (/ Got Rhythm changes) - Strike up the Band- Gone with the Wind- I Surrender Dear- I Surrender Dear cont’d - Tea for Two - Tea for Two cont’d - Over the Rainbow (Box 25, Folder 14)
        - “Jazz Combo, 1952” / Alfred H. Bartles; The Manor, Oxford, Mississippi; same recording as Disc 14 (Box 25, Folder 15)
        - “Piano Duo with Dick Handel”; Motel on the Mountain, Rockland, NY, 1962; performance contains Moon River- Tea for Two - [Unknown] - Honeysuckle Rose -Stardust - This Could Be the Start of Something Big - Ebb Tide - [Unknown] - Put on a Happy Face - S’Wonderful - Moon River (reprise) (Box 25, Folder 16)
        - “Dick Handel & Alf Bartles: Piano Duo: Motel on the Mountain”, 1962: [CD transfer] (Box 25, Folder 17)
        - “Arrangements of Alf Bartles” / played by The Jazz Ensemble of Northeast State LA. College, May 17, 1962, Del Sawyer, director; CD-R; 10 tracks (Box 25, Folder 18)
        - “Arrangements of Alf Bartles”, [1962?]; Northeast State Louisiana College Jazz Ensemble (Box 25, Folder 19)
        - “Big Band Arrangements for Northeastern Louisiana State University”, [date illegible] /Alfred H. Bartles; performed by the NELAJazz Ensemble, Del Sawyer, director (Box 25, Folder 20)
        - “SSMF 1975 Comp Program”, 1975; CD transfer (Box 25, Folder 21)
        - “SSMF 1976 Comp Program”, 1976; CD transfer (Box 25, Folder 22)
        - “Alfred Bartles Piano Solos”, Jun. 24-25,1986; recorded in Stuttgart, Germany (Box 25, Folder 23)
        - “AHB at the Piano”; Stuttgart, Germany, June 22-23, 1987; performance contains [Unknown] - Ode to Ray - Ode to Garvín - [Unknown] - Juliana - Sophisticated Lady -Free Improvisation on Sophisticated Lady - [Unidentified free improvisation] - My Heart Belongs to Daddy - You’d Be So Nice to Come Home to - Someone to Watch Over Me - [Unknown] - [Unknown] - [Unknown] - [Unknown] (Box 25, Folder 24)
        - “AHB at the Piano Plays for Del Sawyer”; Stuttgart, Germany, February 4, 1990: performance contains: Every Time We Say Goodbye - All the Things You Are - But Beautiful - Giant Steps - In a Mello [i.e., Mellow] Tone - Day Dream - Don’t You Know I Care - Body and Soul (segue) (Box 25, Folder 25)
        - “AHB at the Piano”; Stuttgart, Germany, December 8, 1990: performance contains: Once I Loved - [Unknown] - In a Mellow Tone - I’m Beginning to See the Light -Sophisticated Lady (segue) - Stardust- [Unknown] - Wien, Wien - It Might as Well be Spring - Sleepy Summer Solitude (AHB=vocal) - Lover Come Back - I Looked for You -Don’t Get Around Much Anymore (Box 25, Folder 26)
        - “AHB at the Piano”; Stuttgart, Germany, May 24, 1992; performance contains: Every Time We Say Goodbye - [Unknown] (Box 25, Folder 27)
        - “Contraband - Swingin’ Low” / various performers. Marcophon; Schweizer Radio DRS, 1993; CD 940-2; contains various works, including: When Tubas Waltz / Alfred Bartels [i.e., Barties] (Box 25, Folder 28)
        - “AHB at the Piano”; Stuttgart, Germany, April 3, 1994: performance contains: [Unknown] - YardbirdSuite (fragment) - [Unknown] - [Unknown] (Box 25, Folder 29)
        - “Three for Two: Duo for Bassoon & Violoncello”, [1998?]: Prof. William Ludwig, bassoon; Julia Barties Emahiser, cello; marked “corrupt” (Box 25, Folder 30)
        - “AHB at the Piano”; Nashville, TN, July 8, 1999: performance contains: Wien, Wien -All the Things You Are - Repetition (Box 25, Folder 31)
        - “Sewanee Summer Music Center, 1999”, July 24,1999; performance includes: Epidaurus / Barties - Three for Two / Barties - Roumanian Dances for Brass Quintet / Bartok, arr. Barties (Box 25, Folder 32)
        - “Alfred Barties”, Jul. 22, 2000: contains: Epidaurus (Brass & Percussion Ensemble of the Sewanee Summer Music Festival, summer 1999) - Lyric Poem for Violin & Piano (Eyal Kless, violin; Martha Barties, piano, Sewanee Summer Music Festival, Jul. 22, 2000) (Box 25, Folder 33)
        - “Alfred H. Barties”; ©2000, ASCAP/GEMA; performance contains: Epidaurus (Brass & Percussion Ensemble of the Sewanee Summer Music Festival) - Three for Two: Duo for Bassoon & Violoncello (Julia Barties Emahiser, cello; Prof. William Ludwig, bassoon) -It Takes Two to Tango/Fishin’ (Jazz Waltz)/Not Really th’ Boogie - Sonata for Chamber Orchestra, opus 1 / Alban Berg/arr. Barties - Alfred Barties Interview with Hans Peter Jahn (copy 1) (Box 25, Folder 34)
        - “Alfred H. Barties”; ©2000, ASCAP/GEMA; performance contains: Epidaurus (Brass & Percussion Ensemble of the Sewanee Summer Music Festival) - Three for Two: Duo for Bassoon & Violoncello (Julia Barties Emahiser, cello; Prof. William Ludwig, bassoon) -It Takes Two to Tango/Fishin’ (Jazz Waltz)/Not Really th’ Boogie - Sonata for Chamber Orchestra, opus 1 / Alban Berg/arr. Barties - Alfred Barties Interview with Hans Peter Jahn (copy 2); marked “Damaged” (Box 25, Folder 35)
        - “Faculty Chamber Concert”, 2000: Harbison - Barties - Debussy (Box 25, Folder 36)
        - “Scherzo - Alfred Barties” / “Dwight Vance-solo; Corvallis Community Band, 5-7-00, 1st Presbyterian Church, Corvallis, OR”: CD-R, includes brief note from the soloist; disc not finalized and will not play (Box 25, Folder 37)
        - “Symphonia3: Symphonia Fantastique!” Mark, 2001: contains various works, including The New “When Tubas Waltz” / Alfred Barties (Box 25, Folder 38)
        - “Eugene Symphonic Band”; Spring Concert, 5/14/2002, Robert Ponto, conductor; CD-R; performance includes Scherzo for Tuba & Symphonic Band / Alfred H. Barties (Box 25, Folder 39)
        - ‘Tim Northcut & The TTU Symphony Band”; “Complete CD edited v. 2, 6/29/02”; CD-R; performance includes Tubossa / Barties (Box 25, Folder 40)
        - “Sewanee Summer Music Festival”; The Festival Chamber Orchestra, The Sewanee Symphony, Sunday, July 14, 2002, Guerry Hall; 2 CD set; performance includes Sonata I Alban Berg; arr. Alfred Barties (Box 25, Folder 41)
        - “Sewanee Summer Music Festival”, Jul. 14, 2002; includes: Sonata / Berg/Bartles (Box 25, Folder 42)
        - ‘Tennessee Tech Pride” / featuring Timothy Northcut, tubist with the TTU Symphony Band, Joseph Hermann, conductor. Mark Custom Recording Service, (P)2003; 4371-MCD; performance includes: Tubossa: a Concerto Bossa nova for Solo Tuba and Symphonic Band / Alfred Barties; insert signed by Timothy Northcut (Box 25, Folder 43)
        - “Lyric Poem for Violin and Piano”, Jul. 22, 2000: Faculty Chamber Concert, Sewanee Music Festival; Eyal Kless, violin; Martha Bartles, piano (Box 25, Folder 44)
        - “Music for Symphony Orchestra & Jazz Ensemble”, Nov. 26, 2002: recorded by the Nashville Symphony & The Jazz Machine, Jay Dawson, director (Box 25, Folder 45)
        - “SSMF Faculty Chamber Music” Aug. 2, 2003: includes Bartles’s First Rhapsody for Cello & Orchestra [arrangement] (Box 25, Folder 46)
        - ‘Tennessee Tech Tuba Ensemble presents... Vintage”. R. Winston Morris, director. Mark Custom Recording Service, (P)2006; 6736-MCD: performance includes: When Tubas Waltz / Alfred H. Bartles (copy 1) (Box 25, Folder 47)
        - ‘Tennessee Tech Tuba Ensemble presents... Vintage”. R. Winston Morris, director. Mark Custom Recording Service, (P)2006; 6736-MCD: performance includes: When Tubas Waltz / Alfred H. Bartles (copy 2) (Box 25, Folder 48)
        - “Pre-European Tour Concert 1963”; Northeast Louisiana State College Jazz Ensemble directed by John F. Sawyer, arrangements by Alfred H. Bartles; performance includes: Theme [from Turning Up] - Mr. Lucky - Louisiana Jazz Suite (parts 1 and 2) -Jordu-Dahaud- Captain Ahab - Lady Be Good - Metamorphosis of Time after Time - From this Moment On - Between the Devil and the Deep Blue Sea. (Box 25, Folder 49)
        - “And Well I Shall Be There”, [n.d.]; Nashville Youth Symphony, McGavock Choir, Jay Dawson, director (Box 25, Folder 50)
        - “AHB_2”, [n.d.]: listed contents: Pno_l - Pno_2 (Box 25, Folder 51)
        - “AHB_3”, [n.d.]: listed contents: Pno_4 - Pnojune 87 (Box 25, Folder 52)
        - “AHB_4”, [n.d.]: listed contents: Pno_92 - Plays for Del (Box 25, Folder 53)
        - “AHB_7”, [n.d.]: listed contents: Big Band, Nashville Sym., NELA (Box 25, Folder 54)
        - “Lyric Poem PDF file”, [n.d.] (Box 25, Folder 55)
        - “Alf Bartles Yardbird/Out of this World PDF & Finale 2002” (Box 25, Folder 56)
        - “Encore files—Scherzo, A. Bartles”, 3Vz” floppy disc (Box 25, Folder 57)
      - Compact discs/CD-ROMs/Other (Box 26)
        - [digital transfer of Reel 1 from Box 22] (Box 26, Folder 1)
        - [digital transfer of Reel 2 from Box 22] (Box 26, Folder 2)
        - [digital transfer of Reel 3 from Box 22] (Box 26, Folder 3)
        - [digital transfer of Reel 4 from Box 22] (Box 26, Folder 4)
        - [digital transfer of Reel 5 from Box 22] (Box 26, Folder 5)
        - [digital transfer of Reel 6 from Box 22] (Box 26, Folder 6)
        - [digital transfer of Reel 7 from Box 22] (Box 26, Folder 7)
        - [digital transfer of Reel 8 from Box 22] (Box 26, Folder 8)
        - [digital transfer of Reel 9 from Box 22] (Box 26, Folder 9)
        - [digital transfer of Reel 10 from Box 22] (Box 26, Folder 10)
        - [digital transfer of Reel 11 from Box 22] (Box 26, Folder 11)
        - [digital transfer of Reel 12 from Box 22] (Box 26, Folder 12)
        - [digital transfer of Reel 13 from Box 22] (Box 26, Folder 13)
        - [digital transfer of Reel 14 from Box 22] (Box 26, Folder 14)
        - [digital transfer of Reel 15 from Box 22] (Box 26, Folder 15)
        - [digital transfer of Reel 16 from Box 22] (Box 26, Folder 16)
        - [digital transfer of Reel 17 from Box 22] (Box 26, Folder 17)
        - [digital transfer of Reel 18 from Box 22] (Box 26, Folder 18)
        - [digital transfer of Reel 19 from Box 22] (Box 26, Folder 19)
        - [digital transfer of Reel 20 from Box 22] (Box 26, Folder 20)
        - [digital transfer of Reel 21 from Box 22] (Box 26, Folder 21)
        - [digital transfer of Reel 22 from Box 22] (Box 26, Folder 22)
        - [digital transfer of Reel 23 from Box 22] (Box 26, Folder 23)
        - [digital transfer of Reel 24 from Box 22]; copy #1 (Box 26, Folder 24)
        - [digital transfer of Reel 24 from Box 22]; copy #2 (Box 26, Folder 25)
        - [digital transfer of Reel 25 from Box 22]; copy #1 (Box 26, Folder 26)
        - [digital transfer of Reel 25 from Box 22]; copy #2 (Box 26, Folder 27)
        - [digital transfer of Reel 26 from Box 22]; copy #1 (Box 26, Folder 28)
        - [digital transfer of Reel 26 from Box 22]; copy #2 (Box 26, Folder 29)
        - [DVD-R backup of reels 1-2, 4-15] (Box 26, Folder 30)
        - [DVD-R backup of reels 3, 16-23] (Box 26, Folder 31)
  - Series D: Correspondence
    - Subseries 1: Non-Family and Professional
      - Correspondence—Non-Family and Professional Folder (Box 27)